thestretchinghandbook.com 2013-05-13

# Injury Fix™ - Legal Information, Policies and Disclaimers

Trademark  
Injury Fix™ and The Stretching Institute™ are registered trademarks of Walkerbout Health Pty Ltd. International Trademark #: 1 005 350. (United States Trademark Reg. No. 3,752,544) Any unauthorized use of this trademark will be aggressively defended though the appropriate legal processes.

Copyright  
This website and all its content are owned by Walkerbout Health Pty Ltd (Doing Business As) The Stretching Institute and Injury Fix. Copyright © 1995-2012. All rights reserved.

Unless otherwise indicated, all content and materials on this website, including but not limited to the logo, designs, text, graphics, pictures, information, data, software, sound files, other files and the selection and arrangement thereof (collectively, "Website Content") are the proprietary property of Walkerbout Health Pty Ltd or its affiliates, licensors, suppliers or users and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.

The content on this website is monitored and protected by [Copyscape's plagiarism checking software](http://www.copyscape.com/plagiarism-software/). DO NOT COPY OUR CONTENT. If our copyrighted content is found to be published on another website without our prior written approval we will issue a [DMCA](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dmca) (Digital Millennium Copyright Act) Infringement Notification with the offenders hosting provider, and also with [Google](http://www.google.com/support/bin/request.py?contact_type=lr_dmca&product=websearch), [Yahoo!](http://info.yahoo.com/copyright/us/details.html) and [Bing](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cpyrtInfrg.htm).

Disclaimer  
The health and fitness information presented on this website is intended as an educational resource and is not intended as a substitute for proper medical advice. Please consult your physician or physical therapist before performing any of the exercises described on this website, particularly if you are pregnant, elderly or have any chronic or recurring muscle or joint pain. Discontinue any exercise that causes you pain or severe discomfort and consult a medical expert.

Privacy Policy  
Our clients and visitors privacy is an issue we take very seriously. We understand your concerns about the use of your personal and company data, and have formulated this policy to reassure you of how your data will be utilized by us.

What information do we collect?  
We collect information from you when you register on our website, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the "do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  2. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  3. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  4. To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Opt-Out, Unsubscribe and Removal from our database  
Removing your information from our database is easy. At the bottom of every email we send to you are options for unsubscribing and removing your information from our database. Either use the unsubscribe links at the bottom of the email, or submit a ticket via our help desk and one of our staff will remove you from our database.

If you do submit a ticket via our help desk, please make sure you include the email address that you used when you subscribed, purchased one of our products or requested information from us: You can find this address at the bottom of every email we send to you.

Do we use cookies?  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the websites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on websites on the internet.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.
  * You have the option to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/> Alternatively you can opt out of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page. <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Visiting Linked Sites  
Whilst we maintain all measures to protect your privacy, we are unable to monitor or control the Privacy Policies of any of our linked websites. Therefore, we ask that when you visit a linked website, you review the Privacy Policies on the linked website before you disclose any personal or company details there.

NO Spam! Policy  
We actively adhere to all requirement and regulations of the Federal Trade Commission concerning the [CAN-SPAM Act](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/business/ecommerce/bus61.shtm).

Online Privacy Policy Only  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent  
By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on October 18, 2012.

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by submitting an inquiry via our help desk, or using the information below.

**Phone:** | 1-877-580-7771  
---|---  
**Fax:** | 1-646-329-9820  
**Mailing Address:** | Injury Fix  
4747 36th Street  
Suite 3208  
Long Island City, NY 11101  
United States
